{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687089936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687089936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687099833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687099833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687103716","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687103715"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_o-b-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687108597","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687108597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-k-z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687112474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687112474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687118193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687118193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687126495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687126495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-z-d"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687132722","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687132721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-z-d"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687137601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687137601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687145003","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687145003"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687150837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687150837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687159568","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687159568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-a-d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687165259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687165259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-l"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687169564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687169564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-y-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687178434","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687178433"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687182432","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687182431"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687188572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687188572"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-m-f"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687192572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687192571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_y-m-i"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687195913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687195913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-v-k"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687199023","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687199023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-y-w"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687202604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687202604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_t-i-n"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687206901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687206901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-v-e"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687210872","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687210872"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-n-k"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687215154","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687215154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_l-k-j"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687218517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687218517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687222074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687222073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687226088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687226088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-y-h"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687230111","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687230111"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-r-e"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687235925","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687235909"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" d95dd240-3b98-4648-9c4b-d1635e47983e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-r-e"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687247687","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687247687"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687253280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687253280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687258619","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687258619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687265611","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687265611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687270655","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687270655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687275828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687275828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687281165","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687281164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687288073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687288073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687293444","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687293444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687295074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687295073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 04b2bcab-3f79-4e6e-8193-25a3d4ee0971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687313770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687313770"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687315899","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687315899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687318043","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687318043"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687321229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687321229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687323487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687323487"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687325838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687325838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687328681","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687328680"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687330867","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687330866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687333045","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687333045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687336269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687336268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687338386","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687338386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687340506","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687340506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687343503","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687343503"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687351891","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687351890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687354158","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687354157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687357218","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687357218"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687359591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687359591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687361952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687361952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687365093","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687365093"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687367227","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687367227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687369380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687369379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687372525","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687372525"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687374727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687374727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687377254","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687377254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687380411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687380411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687382811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687382811"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687385250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687385250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687388452","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687388451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687390729","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687390729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687393011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687393011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687396168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687396168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687398374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687398374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687400598","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687400597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687403603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687403603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687405933","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687405933"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687408288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687408288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687411410","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687411410"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687413772","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687413772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687416132","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687416132"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687419056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687419056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687421293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687421293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687423547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687423547"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687426724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687426724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687428980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687428980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687431287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687431287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687434586","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687434585"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687436990","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687436990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687439375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687439374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687442194","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687442194"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687444352","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687444351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687446486","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687446485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687449893","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687449893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687452241","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687452240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687454578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687454578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687457724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687457723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687459975","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687459975"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687462252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687462252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687465261","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687465261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687467402","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687467402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687469558","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687469558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687472767","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687472766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687475006","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687475005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687477276","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687477276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687480472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687480472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687482672","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687482672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687484902","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687484902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687488178","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687488177"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687490488","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687490488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687492791","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687492791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687495993","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687495993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687498285","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687498285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687500603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687500603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687503987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687503986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687504102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687504102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687522193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687522192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 0290894f-b85b-4ee5-a33c-518146e96df7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687522294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687522294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 792bcc9e-9af9-410d-8c22-6098845aef05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687541600","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687541600"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687555885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687555885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687557443","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687557443"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687567653","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687567652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687567826","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687567826"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687590913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687590913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687598318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687598318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687606833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687606832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 2503c3cd-fd9b-44bd-b6fe-ceae16224162"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687641212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687641211"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" a8ae81b3-23fb-424d-839f-abd3a0fadfff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_pa-mlima-mtini-kina"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" kina"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687643916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687643916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" a8ae81b3-23fb-424d-839f-abd3a0fadfff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_pa-mlima-mtini-kina"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" mtini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687650117","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687650116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" a8ae81b3-23fb-424d-839f-abd3a0fadfff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mtini_pa-mlima-mtini-kina"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687650232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687650232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" a8ae81b3-23fb-424d-839f-abd3a0fadfff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687662499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687662499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" a8ae81b3-23fb-424d-839f-abd3a0fadfff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687679948","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687679947"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687687290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687687290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687693391","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687693391"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687705779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687705778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687762792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687762791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687769819","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687769819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-1-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687798082","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687798082"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687817626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687817626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687824361","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687824361"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687831452","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687831451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687842986","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687842986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687848924","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687848924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687855670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687855669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ba4aea66-731c-4904-8b87-fcc7b90b77da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687904133","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687904132"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687910828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687910828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687917538","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687917538"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_a_n"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687924295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687924294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687931033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687931032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687937770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687937770"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687945370","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687945370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687955729","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687955729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687961994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687961994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_u_a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687968733","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687968732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_b_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687975446","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687975445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_y_a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687982154","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687982154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543687991232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543687991232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 4620cb10-5373-4de6-886a-916d1757a749"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688003940","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688003940"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688004794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688004794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688005821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688005821"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688006064","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688006064"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688006621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688006621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688007184","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688007184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688007718","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688007718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688011584","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688011584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688012328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688012328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688012734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688012734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688013548","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688013548"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688014630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688014630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688015425","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688015425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688018721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688018721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688020287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688020286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688023312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688023312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688023576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688023576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688024290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688024290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688025139","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688025139"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688025594","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688025594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688026310","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688026310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688027036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688027035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688028249","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688028249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688031783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688031783"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688032852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688032852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688033413","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688033413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688034020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688034020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688036765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688036764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688036886","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688036886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5efdb65c-8f6b-46d6-a333-07478cabb00f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688062193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688062192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688068892","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688068892"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688075597","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688075595"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_a_n"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688082407","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688082407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688089135","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688089135"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688095852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688095852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688103434","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688103433"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688113779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688113779"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688120485","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688120485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_u_a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688127196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688127196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_b_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688133888","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688133887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_y_a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688140620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688140619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688153684","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688153684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 70302e2b-3893-42af-9e55-662588f70595"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688304879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688304879"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688320143","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688320143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688328119","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688328119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688335420","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688335420"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688344670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688344670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688384107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688384106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688391176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688391175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688397837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688397836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688405125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688405125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688410464","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688410464"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688417158","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688417157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" ac40e5ec-f33d-4886-8165-1d150feadc02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688442706","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688442706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688454935","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688454935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688492291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688492291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688502247","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688502247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688508437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688508437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688520331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688520331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688526297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688526296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688533400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688533400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688541279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688541279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688548396","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688548396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688556235","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688556235"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688563039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688563039"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 47380f1b-1f08-4bf5-b642-59e587f8899a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688577427","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688577427"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688586014","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688586014"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688593794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688593794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688601433","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688601433"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688607459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688607459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688614783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688614782"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688619815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688619815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688626424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688626424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-1-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688633196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688633195"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688640473","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688640473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688646467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688646466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688656621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688656621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688664380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688664380"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688673665","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688673665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688683205","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688683205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688693172","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688693172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 00bc14f8-f9c6-4777-9b09-011ce164c241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688714892","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688714892"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688715479","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688715479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688716397","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688716397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688716545","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688716545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688717251","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688717250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688717947","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688717947"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688718667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688718667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688719248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688719248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688719476","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688719476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688719984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688719984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688723444","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688723444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688723963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688723963"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688724572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688724572"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688725431","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688725431"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688726331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688726330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688729196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688729196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688729622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688729621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688729736","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688729736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688730171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688730171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688730677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688730676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688731452","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688731452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688732121","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688732121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688735572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688735571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688736247","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688736247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688737375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688737375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688737922","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688737922"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688738107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688738107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688738733","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688738733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688739649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688739649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688740438","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688740436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688741125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688741125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688744102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688744101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688745170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688745170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688745963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688745963"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688746127","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688746127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688746553","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688746553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688747645","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688747644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688748867","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688748867"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688749634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688749634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688752555","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688752554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688752945","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688752945"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688753716","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688753716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688754074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688754074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688754727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688754727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688755256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688755256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688755605","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688755605"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688756101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688756101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688756951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688756951"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688757670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688757670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688758203","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688758203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688761627","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688761627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688762633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688762633"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688762863","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688762863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688763424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688763423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688764700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688764700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688765165","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688765165"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688765916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688765916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688766451","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688766451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688766608","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688766608"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688767205","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688767204"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688768070","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688768070"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688771392","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688771392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688772777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688772777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688773730","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688773730"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688776546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688776545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688776764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688776764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 539279f9-dab6-45d3-834e-acb2fd67a001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688790770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688790769"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688791353","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688791353"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688792269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688792269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688792414","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688792413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688793122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688793122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688793807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688793807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688794535","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688794534"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688795118","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688795118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688795347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688795347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688795838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688795838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688799280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688799280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688799797","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688799796"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688800405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688800405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688801211","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688801210"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688802105","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688802105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688805061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688805061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688805486","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688805485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688805604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688805604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688806040","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688806040"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688806547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688806547"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688807322","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688807322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688807991","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688807991"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688811280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688811279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688811953","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688811953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688813082","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688813082"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688813616","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688813616"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688813813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688813812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688814437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688814437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688815352","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688815351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688816133","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688816133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688816820","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688816820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688819789","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688819789"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688820857","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688820856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688821634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688821634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688821799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688821799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688822227","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688822226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688823294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688823294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688824509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688824503"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688825253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688825253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688828188","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688828188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688828542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688828542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688829328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688829328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688829706","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688829706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688830350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688830350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688830874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688830874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688831238","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688831238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688831741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688831741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688832589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688832588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688833307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688833307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688833823","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688833823"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688837168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688837168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688838178","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688838178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688838406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688838405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688838964","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688838964"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688840238","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688840238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688840686","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688840686"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688841439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688841439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688841967","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688841967"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688842124","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688842124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688842723","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688842723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688843601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688843601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688846959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688846959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688848343","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688848343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688849298","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688849297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688852099","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688852099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688852259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688852259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 926b29f2-198c-4fc5-b947-765c961b8577"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688871493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688871492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688872077","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688872077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688872991","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688872991"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688873135","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688873135"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688873840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688873839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688874544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688874544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688875264","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688875263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688875839","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688875839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688876069","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688876069"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688876556","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688876556"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688880024","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688880023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688880539","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688880539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688881146","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688881146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688881950","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688881950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688882845","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688882844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688885831","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688885831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688886257","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688886256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688886371","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688886370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688886827","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688886827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688887331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688887331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688888106","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688888106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688888772","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688888771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688891968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688891967"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688892641","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688892641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688893764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688893764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688894301","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688894300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688894489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688894489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688895115","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688895115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688896036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688896035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688896810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688896810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688897497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688897497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688900497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688900497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688901561","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688901561"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688902337","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688902337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688902505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688902505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688902931","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688902931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688903997","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688903997"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688905204","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688905203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688905950","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688905950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688908935","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688908935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688909292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688909292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688910060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688910060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688910420","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688910420"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688911064","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688911064"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688911591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688911591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688911941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688911941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688912444","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688912444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688913292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688913292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688914009","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688914009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688914528","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688914527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688918020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688918020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688919028","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688919028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688919259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688919259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688919825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688919825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688921102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688921102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688921550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688921550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688922296","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688922296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688922825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688922825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688922983","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688922983"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688923579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688923579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688924444","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688924444"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688927785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688927785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688929170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688929169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688930124","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688930124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688932932","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688932931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688933062","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688933062"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 9968f732-56b7-4df9-b40d-b69a74913056"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688946181","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688946181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688955994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688955994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688957605","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688957604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688963616","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688963616"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688965185","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688965185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688973738","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688973738"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688975332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688975332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688981488","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688981488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688983084","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688983083"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543688989622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543688989622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" START_BARABARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689010387","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689010386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" START_BARABARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689011930","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689011930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689013526","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689013526"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689019693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689019693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689021302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689021302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689031618","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689031617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689033214","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689033213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689047518","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689047517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689047977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689047977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 6143415c-67b8-4156-a950-afaf65cf5621"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689059193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689059193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 79e82f12-7b3e-43f0-9c57-8a1c91a68007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689062054","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689062054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 79e82f12-7b3e-43f0-9c57-8a1c91a68007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689070258","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689070258"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 79e82f12-7b3e-43f0-9c57-8a1c91a68007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689182091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689182091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 79e82f12-7b3e-43f0-9c57-8a1c91a68007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689182328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689182328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 5aec2c7a-cc10-4832-8421-f3419a164cac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689204052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689204052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689210772","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689210772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689217572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689217572"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689224404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689224403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689231182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689231182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689237939","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689237939"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689244751","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689244750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689251491","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689251491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689258404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689258404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689265182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689265182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689278265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689278264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689286068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689286068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_205658"," gameId":" 52f183bd-99c7-455d-8868-e481a46bde31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}